All right, so let's test this out by first going over to the project, see make this file.
And here, let's change the project file name to firmware update test.
All right, now, let's go to Wi-Fi outreach, and let's change the society to farmer update test.
All right, now, let's go to the stylesheet and we could change the background color to something else.
I'll just use two two two two two two and then just build the project.
All right, so now let's just give this a chance to build.
And meanwhile, I can show you with the application file is so just follow me here.
We're going to go to the Build folder.
All right, so that's the build folder.
We're just going to wait for the build to finish so we can grab our firmware update.
Test bin file.
OK, so now it's done, let's go grab the test file.
All right, so here it is.
Let's just keep that somewhere easy to find.
OK, so now we can just go undo all of our changes, so let's undo what we did to the stylesheet.
And change the suicide back as well, and here and let's also change the file name back to normal.
And then let's build again.
OK, so now we can open up Google Chrome.
All right, so once the build finishes, we can flush it.
So go ahead and flush.
OK, so we're flesh, and now we can open up a monitor so we can check out what's going on.
Well, we have the web page open as well.
All right, so now we need to connect to the ESP.
So let's go down to the available Wi-Fi networks.
Let's connect to our ISP, the normalises side.
OK, so now let's go to our IP address.
OK, very cool, we have our date and time showing up right here.
Now, let's select the file.
And minus here somewhere on the desktop.
OK.
There's my firmware update spin.
OK, so now we have the file size right there now click update firmware.
Now we could see in the monitor that we're receiving the file.
But on the web page, it's already showing that the firmware update is completed, so the monitor is
lagging, probably due to the repeated print deaths.
So anyway, great, the ESP is now rebooting.
And if we reconnect.
So now let's let's reconnect to the firmware update test as this idea.
That's our test as a side.
So connect to it.
And then let's open up the Web page again.
All right, great.
Now we can confirm that a firmware update application is indeed running well done.